[dramatic music playing]
[Killua] I beat him
right here and now,
or it's all over!
I've gotta protect Gon,
no matter what it takes!
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
FRIEND X AND X JOURNEY
[narrator] Killua prepares
for a fight with a Chimera Ant,
fiercely determined
to protect Gon
for the 30 days
he is unable to use Nen.
However…
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[Illumi] Run.
[gasping]
[breathing shakily]
[laughing]
Perfect! That's more like it,
that terrified expression.
I love that one!
[laughs] Oh, yeah.
Now I really feel like killing you.
[laughs]
I'm gonna crush you
into a bloody pulp.
[Illumi] Avoid battles
you can't be sure you'll win.
[Killua] I have to protect him.
I have to!
[Illumi] When your enemy is unknown…
[Killua] Protect Gon…
[Illumi] …run away.
[Killua] No matter what happens!
[yells]
[gasps]
[shuddering]
-[serene music playing]
-[insects chirping]
Mm?
Is this tree special?
Just a little longer.
You'll see.
[sighs]
[chirping changes]
[gasps]
[both chuckle]
Wow!
Sea fireflies.
They like to live near brackish water,
and it's breeding season.
[Palm] So pretty.
[Gon] Right?
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[laughs]
Look how scared you are.
Well?
[grunts] Now move!
You can't, can you? Hah!
Since you're frozen with fear!
-[laughing maniacally]
-[Killua grunts]
-[coughing]
-[sighs] Damn.
This feels incredible.
Should I kill him, or savor it?
I can't decide!
[roars]
[Killua grunting]
[Killua coughs]
[shuddering]
[insects chirping]
-[Gon] Here.
-Hmm?
It's a present,
the most beautiful flower
in the world.
[gasps]
Are you sure?
[chuckles]
Now don't move a muscle.
[serene music playing]
-[gasps]
-[serene music continues]
[Palm gasping]
The sap's similar
to the pheromones the fireflies emit,
and that's why they all flock to it.
Beautiful.
[sobbing]
Thank you, Gon.
[Gon] Of course. I'm glad you like it.
But still, I just…
I'd like to give you what you want,
but I can't yet.
[Palm gasps]
What do you think I want?
Time to spend together.
[gasps]
[laughs]
[Killua groans]
[Gon] It's just I want to get stronger,
strong enough to beat the Chimera Ants,
but to do that,
I've gotta train really, really hard.
Kite will be back in two days,
but it sounds like the enemy
is manipulating him.
That means we'll probably
have to fight his controller
to get him back to normal.
Until we do that,
until Kite's himself again,
until we can defeat the Chimera Ants,
I wanna focus on my training.
[Rammot yells]
[Killua grunts]
Yes! Yes! That's it!
[laughs]
Will that be okay?
Huh? What the hell?
[yells]
Damn it! I can't get enough!
[Illumi] Run.
-[gasps]
-[Illumi] Hurry.
[Killua] No.
-[shattering noise]
-[gasps, grunts]
Gon…
[grunts]
I will…
[laughs]
[Killua] …protect you.
Because…
Because we're friends!
Do you hear me, Gon?
-You're my best friend!
-[gasps]
Stop that right now.
Don't look at me like that.
I can't hold it anymore.
I'm gonna do it.
I've gotta…
[Illumi] Run.
[Killua] Shut up!
[shattering noise]
[Illumi] Run.
[Killua] You can't tell me what--
[shattering]
[Illumi] Run. Run. Run.
[Killua] Shut up!
[shattering]
I'll just leave the head,
and I'll eat the rest!
[Illumi] Run.
[Killua] I don't ever want to lose him!
[yells]
[Illumi] Run.
[Killua] Gon is…
[Killua] He's my…
[Gon] Run.
[Killua] He's my best…
[Illumi] Run.
I can't do this without Killua!
[dramatic music playing]
[Killua] Gon is…
my best friend!
[yells]
Huh?
He's gone?
Huh.
Eh?
[chuckling]
[laughs]
He got me.
Damn, Illumi.
Why the hell didn't I catch this before?
He planted this deep inside my brain.
Huh? What are you saying?
Are you nuts?
Also, how were you able to dodge that?
Wait. I saw the whole thing.
Right as I was preparing to strike,
he stabbed his finger into his own head.
Then he vanished,
and now he's standing
right over there.
[Killua sighs]
I feel so much better now.
It's like I'm finally awake again.
No. It's more like
I've finally been freed.
[Rammot] That's all that happened, so how…
[gasps]
It has to be my imagination.
Why am I the one
who's suddenly paralyzed with fear?
Now go and tell the other Ants.
If they even come near us,
they're all gonna end up dead.
[Rammot gasping]
[yelling] Why you--
That so?
[Killua] Fine. Who cares?
[grass rustling]
[panting]
They're gone.
Their stuff's still here.
Wait. Did another Ant…
I don't sense any. That means…
[gasps]
[ominous music playing]
Eh?
What are you doing?
What? Can't you tell?
This is his punishment.
His punishment for hurting my feelings,
that's what!
Well, knock it off!
You're the one who's
being unreasonable here.
Can't you see that?
[Killua] Well, at least he's okay.
You just stay out of it!
This is none of your business!
Oh, yeah? Well, right back at you, idiot.
Why don't you just go away?
[gasps]
Hmm?
Where did you get those wounds?
Hmm? Oh.
I was training. Is that okay?
[Palm] Let me give you some more!
[Gon] Palm!
It's fine.
Your knife's pretty slow.
Could dodge it in my sleep.
[Palm groans]
I was so sure I got him.
[groans]
[yells]
[yelps]
[dramatic music playing]
[Palm] Come back here
so I can kill you!
[panting]
[gasping]
[gasps]
Oh, yeah? Well, just catch us
if you can, you idiot!
[dramatic music playing]
Wait right there, you little…
You've gotta stop, Killua.
Running away's only
gonna make her a lot angrier.
Huh? But if we ditch her,
we won't have to see her again!
Look, we're gonna
have to call up Knuckle
and tell him that
we've gotta figure out
someplace else
to meet up with him and Kite.
Sorry, but I'm going back.
You wanna die?
'Cause that's what's gonna happen.
If you let your guard down,
thinking she's not much of a fighter,
she's gonna stab you in the back!
[Gon laughs]
No, she'd never do that.
[Killua] Huh? But…
didn't you just see her
take that knife to me?
Damn it, Gon! You're too much.
You know that?
[panting]
So you think you got the better of me?
[yells maniacally]
[running footsteps]
[yells]
[panting]
You think you got away?
You're wrong, fool.
I can find you anywhere!
[laughs]
[panting]
[breathing raggedly]
My dear, dear little mermaid,
find that infernal brat, Killua.
Where'd he go?
There he is, the fool.
The hotel by the train station.
You brat. Brat, brat, brat!
Always interrupting!
[shudders] If it weren't for him,
everything would be perfect!
[yells]
[laughs maniacally]
I'll hunt you down
wherever you go! I promise!
You won't beat me!
[shrieks]
[gasps]
Master Knov.
Where did those boys run off to?
Oh! Right.
They both went to the hotel
that has a logo
with three circles on it.
[cell phone beeps]
Knov again.
They went to the Tri-Orb hotel.
[Morel] Yeah. As a matter of fact,
we just got a call from them.
Oh. Uh, I believe
you had planned the rendezvous
in two days?
No. We're on schedule.
We'll utilize the extra two days
to observe them,
determine if they're ready
to see Kite in his current condition.
[whimpering]
-But first things first, Ms. Palm.
-[Palm] Yes?
It appears that you used your ability
without my permission.
[Palm shudders]
I thought I said,
"Prepare for the unexpected,
and just wait for my orders"?
Right.
You must realize
that your blood is a precious resource.
[gasps] Did he say, "precious"?
[dramatic music playing]
You must use it only for me.
[Palm] Yes, only for Master Knov.
Got it?
[Palm gasps] Yes!
[sighs]
Master Knov really
is the only one for me.
What's with the clothes?
It's quite a look.
Eh? This old thing?
Uh, just dressing up. No reason.
[laughing nervously]
He called me precious.
Then just tell her to wait!
For a while, anyway,
until Kite is back to normal.
I already did that.
[groans]
[narrator] Gon Freecss,
age 12, blood type "B,"
forced to briefly "date" Palm Siberia,
age 22, blood type "A,"
then dumped without warning.
[dramatic music playing]
[shuddering]
Damn. This one again?
That's three now.
Hmm.
-Hmm?
-Hey! The secret one!
Huh? Are you sure?
Yeah! It's worth a lot.
Sell it online,
and you can make a killing.
Nah. You take it.
Not interested.
[laughs]
Did something happen?
Huh? Not really.
Hmm.
Now come on.
Let's go hit up the gym.
Sure!
[shudders]
-[Knov] How's it going?
-[gasps] Huh?
Fine. Nothing yet.
They seem to be doing well.
Of course, we should
continue to observe them.
They have business to attend to,
so we'll give them time.
[narrator] While Knov and Shoot
were observing
Gon and Killua's mental state…
Huh?
He's here.
[dramatic music playing]
Hmm.
[grunts]
[Cheetu] Who the hell is he?
Hey, not bad.
[yells]
[both grunt]
He's fast.
You're a lot faster
than the guys from yesterday…
but not by much, I'm afraid.
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "Grudge and Dread."
[grunts] Another order of steak, please!
-[Killua] You sure eat a lot.
-[Gon] Don't hold a grudge!
[Killua] That doesn't really make sense.
[singer singing in Japanese]